

# **Marion Judy**

(760) 213-9494 • marionejudy@gmail.com • marionjudy.dev

# **Summary:**

Innovative, passionate and driven leader that loves collaborating with peers to deliver results. Offering 6 years of combined technical and design development. Looking for new opportunities to expand my technical skill set, leadership experience and to contribute to a great team.

# **Relevant Skills:**

- Project leadership and ownership
- Self-managed and organized
- Solid programming foundation in React.js, Next.js, Sanity.io, HTML, CSS, and Javascript
- Experience working in Agile and Scrum environments
- Experience working with content management systems and databases (Sanity.io, Netlify CMS, WordPress, Webflow, GraphQL)
- Advanced skills developing with a mobile-first and responsive approach
- Understanding of optimizing sites and webpages for performance, page speed, and SEO
- Experience working with APIs
- Experience with CLI and GIT including git flow branching merging and resolving conflicts.
- Proficient working with UI and CSS frameworks like Foundation and Tailwind CSS
- Advanced experience with low-code and design tooling (Adobe CC, Figma, Webflow, Wordpress)
- Strong communication skills

# **Work Experience:**

### Frontend Web Developer, Independent Contractor

November 2017 - Present | Remote

- Specializing in designing, building, and maintaining affordable websites for small businesses.
- Developing using a variety of tooling including Webflow, Wordpress, React, Next.js, Sanity, Gatsby, Netlify, and Foundation.
- Providing technical support to clients.
- Helped save clients up to \$4,995 on hosting expenses.

# Frontend Web Developer, Redstitch Digital Marketing Agency

November 2019 - May 2021 | Evansville, Indiana

- Assisted in building multiple sites with React and Gatsby.
- Managed monthly upkeep for 15 websites with various platforms including React/Gatsby sites and headless and traditional Wordpress sites with both custom and templated themes. Implemented a system using automation to reduce the likelihood of clientside errors and decreased overall monthly development time.
- Setup deployment pipelines using Deploy HQ, Netlify, and Github.
- Planned and developed several Wordpress site builds with extremely tight turnarounds.
- Created technical documentation for each client site.

#### Founder & Director, Tertia

Fanuary 2016 - Present | Evansville, Indiana

- Developed a peer-led challenge and adventure-based support group for female-oriented survivors of domestic violence and sexual assault.
- Managed the organization's board, fundraising, finances, program scheduling, and outreach events.
- Created the organization's brand and brand collaterals including the logo, website, print material, and outreach booth.

## **Graphic Designer, Escalade Sports**

March 2014 - May 2016 | Evansville, Indiana

- Created branding for new product lines and assisted with product development.
- Designed websites, ads, catalogs, packaging and promotional material for 28 sports brands.
- Created branded displays according to retail customer concept.
- Team helped offset \$1.2M annual agency spend.

# **Education:**

#### University of Southern Indiana: Bachelor's of Science

Fine Arts (Emphasis on Graphic Design and Interactive Media)

# **Awards:**

- 2020 Celebration of Leadership Award: Tertia
- 2018 Silver Award EDG Awards: Hutsoninc.com
- 2017 Judge's Choice EDG Awards: Winter Solstice Open House Invitation
- 2017 Gold EDG Awards: Winter Solstice Open House Invitation
- 2016 Gold AAF Awards: Smarter Games Logo
- 2015 Silver Award EDG Awards: Brand Creation & Execution for Viva Sol